<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Experiments in Automation</title>
    <link>https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Experiments in Automation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 13:52:47 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Automating Habit Tracking using Habitify and Siri Shortcuts</title>
      <link>https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/automating-habits/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Sep 2019 13:52:47 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/automating-habits/</guid>
      <description>Introduction As countless books may tell you, habits are the key to success. These small behaviors that one works into their lifestyle over time can make dramatic changes down the line. Much like the power of compounding interest in the bank, habits are like the daily deposits we make into the account of life.
Ideally, habits are automated. That is, they become so ingrained in our lifestyles and psyches that we don&amp;rsquo;t even think twice about doing them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Siri Shortcuts: A Great Start, But Falls Short in Its Purpose</title>
      <link>https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/siri-shortcuts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Nov 2018 19:17:35 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://miloszkowal.github.io/posts/siri-shortcuts/</guid>
      <description>Introduction With iOS 12, Apple finally told us what they’re doing with their acquisition of Workflow. The answer came in the form of Siri Shortcuts, a whole new app (really just an update to the existing Workflow app), which promised automation capabilities that could be triggered with the world’s fickle digital assistant. Shortly after the first beta releases of iOS 12 were available to developers and to the public, Apple released the Siri Shortcuts beta to developers so that they could adapt their apps to the new Siri APIs.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>